Guide to the Sarenco Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1964-2012; Series I
  - 463-Rosa Foschi, 1997 February 7 (Box 1)
  - 464-Sergio Cena, 1997 February 13 (Box 1)
  - 465-Peter Spence, undated (Box 1)
  - 466-Luciano Caruso, 1997 February 9 (Box 1)
  - 467-Fernando Millan, 1997 (Box 1)
  - 468-Claudio Francia, 1997 February 14 (Box 1)
  - 469-Giovanni Fontana, 2006 December 2 (Box 1)
  - 470-Lucia Marcucci, 2007 January 5 (Box 1)
  - 471-BAU, 2007 March 13 (Box 1)
  - 472-BAU, 2007 October 3 (Box 1)
  - 473-BAU, 2007 September 20 (Box 1)
  - 474-Neide De Sà/Alvaro De Sà, 1994 May 20 (Box 1)
  - 475-Julio Campal, 1967 November 5 (Box 1)
  - 476-Julio Campal, undated (Box 1)
  - 477-Julio Campal, 1966 May 3 (Box 1)
  - 478-Pierre Garnier, 2003 September 30 (Box 1)
  - 479-Pierre Garnier, 2003 May 22 (Box 1)
  - 480-Aldo Tagliaferri, 2005 January 2 (Box 1)
  - 481-Aldo Tagliaferri, 2003 January 7 (Box 1)
  - 482-Harald Szeemann, undated (Box 1)
  - 483-Fernando Millan, 2001 September 3 (Box 1)
  - 484-Nahl Nucha, 1998 May 8 (Box 1)
  - 485-Sergio Dangelo, 1998 February 23 (Box 1)
  - 486-Lamberto Pignotti, 1998 (Box 1)
  - 487-Neide Dias De Sa, 1998 November 4 (Box 1)
  - 488-Ladislav Novak, 1998 November 6 (Box 1)
  - 489-Bohumila Groegerova/Josef Hirsal, 1999 March 6 (Box 1)
  - 490-Takahashi Shoachiro, 1999 March 18 (Box 1)
  - 491-Robin Crozier, 1999 February 20 (Box 1)
  - 492-Ladislav Novak, 1999 May 6 (Box 1)
  - 493-Jean François Bory, 2001 June 18 (Box 1)
  - 494-Ilse Garnier, 1999 November 19 (Box 1)
  - 495-Ugo Carrega, 2001 July 7 (Box 1)
  - 496-Harald Szeemann, 2001 November 9 (Box 1)
  - 497-Harald Szeemann, 2001 July 22 (Box 1)
  - 498-Monty Cantsin, 1999 June 27 (Box 1)
  - 499-Ugo Carrega, 2004 October 22 (Box 1)
  - 500-Jean-François Bory, 2004 October 7 (Box 1)
  - 501-Alvaro De Sà/Neide De Sà, 1999 March 13 (Box 1)
  - 502-Julien Blaine, 1999 April 26 (Box 1)
  - 503-Bern Porter, 1999 July 6 (Box 1)
  - 504-Emmett Williams, undated (Box 1)
  - 505-Arrigo Lora-Totino, 1998 May 12 (Box 1)
  - 506-Julien Blaine, 2006 March 10 (Box 1)
  - 507-Lamberto Pignotti, 2009 (Box 1)
  - 508-Takahashi Shoachiro, 2006 April 7 (Box 1)
  - 509-Philippe Castellin, undated (Box 1)
  - 510-Jean-François Bory, 2005 July 17 (Box 1)
  - 511-Graciela Gutierrez Marx, 2006 January 22 (Box 1)
  - 512-Piero Cavellini, 2006 February 24 (Box 1)
  - 513-Albrecht/d., 2006 August 8 (Box 1)
  - 514-Luc Fierens, 2005 December 24 (Box 1)
  - 515-Francesco Conz, 2005 December 19 (Box 1)
  - 516-Giovanni Fontana, 1999 November 22 (Box 1)
  - 517-Ann Noel, 1999 October 3 (Box 1)
  - 518-Eugenio Miccini, 2005 May 16 (Box 1)
  - 519-Jiri Valoch, 2005 May 26 (Box 1)
  - 520-Pierre Garnier, 2007 November 25 (Box 1)
  - 521-Ilse Garnier, 2005 May 21 (Box 1)
  - 522-Jean-François Bory, 2008 February 14 (Box 1)
  - 523-Camila Rocha, 2008 April 9 (Box 1)
  - 524-Heinz Gappmayr, 2005 November 26 (Box 1)
  - 525-Ugo Carrega, undated (Box 1)
  - 526-Emmett Williams, 2006 (Box 1)
  - 527-Ingeborg Luescher, 2007 September 20 (Box 1)
  - 528-Bernard Aubertin, 2007 August 22 (Box 1)
  - 529-Stelio Maria Martini, 2007 July 3 (Box 1)
  - 530-E.M. De Melo e Castro, 1994 May 4 (Box 1)
  - 531-Lamberto Pignotti, 1994 (Box 1)
  - 532-Bartolome Ferrando, undated (Box 1)
  - 533-Bernard Heidsieck, 1994 April 17 (Box 1)
  - 534-Carlfriedrich Claus, 1994 May 5 (Box 1)
  - 535-Edgardo Antonio Vigo, 2000 May 11 (Box 1)
  - 536-Edgardo Antonio Vigo, 2000 June 14 (Box 1)
  - 537-Emmett Williams, 1992 March 6 (Box 1)
  - 538-Edgardo Antonio Vigo, 2000 November 8 (Box 1)
  - 539-Fernando Aguiar, 1987 January 11 (Box 1)
  - 540-Anna Oberto, 1996 June 28 (Box 1)
  - 541-Edgardo Antonio Vigo, 2000 January 7 (Box 1)
  - 542-Joan Brossa, 1997 March 9 (Box 1)
  - 543-John Furnival, 1997 October 31 (Box 1)
  - 544-John Furnival, 2006 May 7 (Box 1)
  - 545-Hansjorg Mayer, 2005 December 7 (Box 1)
  - 546-Albrecht/d., 2006 February 22 (Box 1)
  - 547-Bohumila Groegerova, 2006 February 26 (Box 1)
  - 547-Nicholas Zurbrugg, 1997 November 14 (Box 1)
  - 548-Felix Guattari, undated (Box 1)
  - 549-Dietrich Mahlow, 1988 January 19 (Box 1)
  - 550-Jiri Kolar, 1986 February 10 (Box 1)
  - 551-Dick Higgins, 1986 April 18 (Box 1)
  - 552-Alain Arias-Misson, 1985 (Box 1)
  - 553-Dick Higgins, 1987 March 27 (Box 1)
  - 554-Jiri Valoch, 1987 February 6 (Box 1)
  - 555-Ugo Carrega, 1987 February 20 (Box 1)
  - 556-Tadeusz Kantor, 1985 October 3 (Box 1)
  - 557-Arturo Schwarz, 1986 January 21 (Box 1)
  - 558-Guggenheim Museum, 1988 October 20 (Box 1)
  - 559-Theodore Koenig, 1988 November 24 (Box 1)
  - 560-Jean François Bory, 1989 May 14 (Box 1)
  - 561-Ben Vautier, 1982 September 5 (Box 1)
  - 562-Patrizia Vicinelli, 1984 July 30 (Box 1)
  - 563-Adriano Spatola, 1978 September 19 (Box 1)
  - 564-René Block, 1983 June 21 (Box 1)
  - 565-Enrico Baj, 1983 November 28 (Box 1)
  - 566-Meret Oppenheim, 1983 February 26 (Box 1)
  - 567-Robert Motherwell, 1983 February 28 (Box 1)
  - 568-Wolf Vostell, 1983 June 16 (Box 1)
  - 569-Roland Werro, 1983 November 11 (Box 1)
  - 570-Emmett Williams, 1983 April 12 (Box 1)
  - 571-Josef Hirsal/Bohumila Groegerova, 1994 May 6 (Box 1)
  - 572-Eugenio Miccini, undated (Box 1)
- Typewriter poems, 1957-2006; Series II
  Organized by artist.
  - Ilse Garnier
    - 1- Visible/Invisible, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 2- Strates, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 3-Vegetal, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 4-Sommer, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 5-Terre, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 6-Labyrinth, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 7-Schatten, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 8-Spuren, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 9-Knospen, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 10-Tangente, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 11-Knospen, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 12-Sommer, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 13-V, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 14-Humus, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 15-Innen/Aussen, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 16-Strates, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 17-Keimung, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 18-Jehann la bonne Lorraine, 1967 (Box 2)
    - 19-La roue de fortune, 1967 (Box 2)
    - 20-La blason de la peste, 1967 (Box 2)
    - 21-Tamerlan, 1967 (Box 2)
    - 22-Quand reviendrai-je ici filer encore la laine, 1967 (Box 2)
    - 23-La defaite des chevalier teutoniques à Tannenburg, 1967 (Box 2)
    - 24-Les compagnons de Jeanne, 1967 (Box 2)
    - 25-E, 1967 (Box 2)
    - 26-E, 1967 (Box 2)
    - 27-E, 1967 (Box 2)
    - 28-Vegetal, 1967 (Box 2)
    - 29-Mineral, 1967 (Box 2)
    - 30-1967 (Box 2)
    - 31-Voice, 1967 (Box 2)
  - Demosthenese Agrafiotis
    - 1-Purple Alphabet, 2006 (Box 2)
    - 2-Purple Alphabet, 2006 (Box 2)
    - 3-Purple Alphabet, 2006 (Box 2)
    - 4-Purple Alphabet, 2006 (Box 2)
    - 5-Purple Alphabet, 2006 (Box 2)
    - 6-Purple Alphabet, 2006 (Box 2)
    - 7-Purple Alphabet, 2006 (Box 2)
    - 8-Purple Alphabet, 2006 (Box 2)
    - 9-Purple Alphabet, 2006 (Box 2)
    - 10-Purple Alphabet, 2006 (Box 2)
    - 11-Purple Alphabet, 2006 (Box 2)
    - 12-Purple Alphabet, 2006 (Box 2)
    - 13-Purple Alphabet, 2006 (Box 2)
    - 14-Purple Alphabet, 2006 (Box 2)
    - 15-Purple Alphabet, 2006 (Box 2)
    - 16-Purple Alphabet, 2006 (Box 2)
    - 17-Purple Alphabet, 2006 (Box 2)
    - 18-Purple Alphabet, 2006 (Box 2)
    - 19-Purple Alphabet, 2006 (Box 2)
    - 20-Purple Alphabet, 2006 (Box 2)
    - 21-Purple Alphabet, 2006 (Box 2)
    - 22-Purple Alphabet, 2006 (Box 2)
    - 23-Purple Alphabet, 2006 (Box 2)
    - 24-Purple Alphabet, 2006 (Box 2)
    - 25-Purple Alphabet, 2006 (Box 2)
    - 26-Purple Alphabet, 2006 (Box 2)
    - 27-Purple Alphabet, 2006 (Box 2)
    - 28-Purple Alphabet, 2006 (Box 2)
    - 29-Purple Alphabet, 2006 (Box 2)
    - 30-Purple Alphabet, 2006 (Box 2)
  - Pierre Garnier
    - 1-Cosmos, 1970 (Box 2)
    - 2-Forets, 1970 (Box 2)
    - 3-Arbre, 1970 (Box 2)
    - 4-Montagne, 1970 (Box 2)
    - 5-Lune, 1970 (Box 2)
    - 6-Pluie, 1970 (Box 2)
    - 7-Feuillage, 1970 (Box 2)
    - 8-Demoiselle, Jardin, Colline, 1970 (Box 2)
    - 9-Neige, phoque, feu, mani, 1970 (Box 2)
    - 10-Yeux, hirondelle, terre, rivière, 1970 (Box 2)
    - 11-Jeu, la lune, poussière, cosmos, 1970 (Box 2)
    - 12-Reveries, oeil, écuroeil, eau, 1970 (Box 2)
    - 13-Ylse, harpe, la voile, elle, 1970 (Box 2)
    - 14-Ciel, lune, sauleille, herbe, lanterne, 1970 (Box 2)
    - 15-Sainte-Jeanne, Vierge Solare, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 16-L'ange de l'Annonciation, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 17-Marie, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 18-Etoile de la natività, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 19-Les insignes de l'Empire, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 20-Reve d'Othon III, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 21-Portrait d'Olaf, Brian, Svend, Waik, d'un Polonais, d'un Bohemien, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 22-Ekkehart, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 23-Visite à Charlemagne en son tombeau d'Aix, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 24-Le 20 juin 1942 à 9 heures 32 une mouche est morte de cette déchirure, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 25-Immobile éternité, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 26-Winkelmesser, 1965 (Box 2)
  - Henri Chopin
    - 1-Le palais sevère 1984 (Box 2)
    - 2-Dynamisme 1984 (Box 2)
    - 3-A very placid city 1984 (Box 2)
    - 4-Cubes dansants 1984 (Box 2)
  - Sarenco
    - 1-Aria, 1969 (Box 2)
    - 2-Fuoco, 1969 (Box 2)
    - 3-Tu, 1969 (Box 2)
    - 4-Mare, 1969 (Box 2)
    - 5-Love, 1969 (Box 2)
    - 6-No, 1969 (Box 2)
    - 7-Cielo, 1969 (Box 2)
    - 8-Terra, 1969 (Box 2)
    - 9-Mettiamo i puntini sulle I, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 10-Sole, 1969 (Box 2)
  - Seiichi Niikuni
    - 1-Mourmour, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 2-Ciel, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 3-Pierre, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 4-Coq, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 5-A, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 6-Eau, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 7-A, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 8-Mer, 1966 (Box 2)
  - Hans Clavin
    - 1-59 Torpedo, 1970 (Box 2)
    - 60-X, 1968 (Box 2)
    - 61- Elvira, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 62-Adventure II 1967 (Box 2)
    - 63-Mn, 1968 (Box 2)
    - 64-Kinetic, 1968 (Box 2)
    - 65-Y.berretty, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 66-Elvira, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 67-Eulachrie, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 68-Poem op, 1967 (Box 2)
    - 69-Luv, 1967 (Box 2)
    - 70-Pqo, 1967 (Box 2)
    - 71-Fonetie/artifone, 1967 (Box 2)
    - 72-Draiboek, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 73-Draiboek, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 74-Poem just, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 75-Coqua, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 76-Grintzee, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 77-Beginselverklaring, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 78-Elvira, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 79-Courti, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 80-Intercollomnium, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 81-Voltage, 1967 (Box 2)
    - 82-Bop, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 83-Rooms lied, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 84-For wise cad ubu, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 85-Yoka Berretty, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 86-Metal pion, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 87-Untitled, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 88-Untitled, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 89-Intercollomnium, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 90-Mini-poem, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 91-None, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 92-Hollandsch allerlei, 1967 (Box 2)
    - 93-Synandrie, 1967 (Box 2)
    - 94-Poeque, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 95-Metapsychese, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 96-Ous oir, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 97-Geldhaan, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 98-Genesis, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 99-Dag doge proto, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 100-Geramtegevaerte, 1967 (Box 2)
    - 101-Age, 1967 (Box 2)
    - 102-Annuciatie, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 103-Ascension, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 104-Mieset, 1967 (Box 2)
    - 105-Luv, 1967 (Box 2)
    - 106-Ji, 1967 (Box 2)
    - 107-Hersteld lied, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 108-The quick brown fox, undated (Box 2)
    - 109- Intercolumnium, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 110-Regeneneren, 1968 (Box 2)
  - Ladislav Novak
    - 1-Eva, 1960-1990 (Box 2)
    - 2-Eva, 1960-1990 (Box 2)
    - 3-Eva, 1960-1990 (Box 2)
    - 4-Eva, 1960-1990 (Box 2)
    - 5-Eva, 1960-1990 (Box 2)
    - 6-Eva, 1960-1990 (Box 2)
    - 7-Individualista, 1959, 1963, 1997 (Box 2)
    - 8-Gloria, 1963 (Box 2)
  - Arrigo Lora-Totino
    - 1-Che tempo fa?, 1960 (Box 2)
    - 2-Il Tempo, 1959 (Box 2)
    - 3-Paradosso, 1959 (Box 2)
    - 4-Le quattro verità, 1958 (Box 2)
    - 5-Niente, 1958 (Box 2)
    - 6-Nevica, 1959 (Box 2)
    - 7-Respiro, 1958 (Box 2)
    - 8-Testo scontroso, 1957 (Box 2)
    - 9-Virtù specchiata, 1957 (Box 2)
    - 10-Vado dove vedo, 1960 (Box 2)
  - Bartolomé Ferrando
    - 1-1982 (Box 2)
    - 2-1982 (Box 2)
    - 3-1982 (Box 2)
    - 4-1977 (Box 2)
    - 5-1977 (Box 2)
    - 6-1977 (Box 2)
    - 7-1978 (Box 2)
    - 8-1978 (Box 2)
    - 9-1978 (Box 2)
- Photographs, circa 1960s-2000s; Series III
  Photographs are arranged in the order in which they were received.
  - 1-Alain Gibertie (Box 3)
  - 2-Alain Gibertie (Box 3)
  - 3-Alain Gibertie (Box 3)
  - 4-Alain Gibertie (Box 3)
  - 5-Alain Gibertie (Box 3)
  - 6-Alain Gibertie (Box 3)
  - 7-Alain Gibertie (Box 3)
  - 8-Aldo Mondino (Box 3)
  - 9-Aldo Mondino (Box 3)
  - 10-Aldo Mondino (Box 3)
  - 11-Aldo Mondino e Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 12-Aldo Mondino e Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 13-Aldo Mondino (Box 3)
  - 14-Aldo Mondino (Box 3)
  - 15-Aldo Mondino (Box 3)
  - 16-Ladislav Novak (Box 3)
  - 17-Ladislav Novak (Box 3)
  - 18-Ladislav Novak e signora (Box 3)
  - 19-Ladislav Novak (Box 3)
  - 20-Ladislav Novak (Box 3)
  - 21-Ladislav Novak e signora (Box 3)
  - 22-Ladislav Novak (Box 3)
  - 23-Ladislav Novak e signora (Box 3)
  - 24-Ladislav Novak (Box 3)
  - 25-Ladislav Novak e signora, Sarenco, 2 sconosciuti (Box 3)
  - 26-Ladislav Novak e Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 27-Ladislav Novak (Box 3)
  - 28-Wolf Vostell (Box 3)
  - 29-Wolf Vostell (Box 3)
  - 30-Wolf Vostell (Box 3)
  - 31-Sarenco, Ladislav Novak e signora (Box 3)
  - 32-Sarenco e Ladislav Novak (Box 3)
  - 33-Ladislav Novak e Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 34-Sarenco e Ladislav Novak (Box 3)
  - 35-Sarenco, Auguste Galli, Ladislav Novak (Box 3)
  - 36-Ladislav Novak e Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 37-Sarenco, signora Novak, Ladislav Novak (Box 3)
  - 38-Sarenco e Ladislav Novak (Box 3)
  - 39-Sarenco, sconosciuto, Auguste Galli, sconosciuto, Franca Vignati, Ladislav Novak (Box 3)
  - 40-Ladislav Novak e Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 41-Ladislav Novak e Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 42-Signora Novak, Ladislav Novak, Franca Vignati, Sarenco, Auguste Galli (Box 3)
  - 43-Sarenco e Ladislav Novak (Box 3)
  - 44-Sarenco e Ladislav Novak (Box 3)
  - 45-Sarenco e Ladislav Novak (Box 3)
  - 46-Ladislav Novak e Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 47-Sarenco e Ladislav Novak (Box 3)
  - 48-Sarenco e Ladislav Novak (Box 3)
  - 49-Alain Gibertie (Box 3)
  - 50-Alain Gibertie (Box 3)
  - 51-Alain Gibertie (Box 3)
  - 52-Alain Gibertie (Box 3)
  - 53-Alain Gibertie (Box 3)
  - 54-Alain Gibertie (Box 3)
  - 55-Alain Gibertie (Box 3)
  - 56-Sarenco: Colognola performance (Box 3)
  - 57-Sarenco, Allahu Akbar, performance (Box 3)
  - 58-Sarenco, Allahu Akbar, performance (Box 3)
  - 59-Sarenco, Allahu Akbar, performance (Box 3)
  - 60-Sarenco, Allahu Akbar, performance (Box 3)
  - 61-Sarenco, Bin Laden performance (Box 3)
  - 62-Sarenco, Bin Laden performance (Box 3)
  - 63-Sarenco, Ventabren performance (Box 3)
  - 64-Sarenco, Harald Szeemann performance (Box 3)
  - 65-Sarenco, Top Model performance (Box 3)
  - 66-Sarenco, Poema gonfiabile (Box 3)
  - 67-Sarenco, Esther Mahlangu, Willy Montini (Box 3)
  - 68-Sarenco, Duchamp performance (Box 3)
  - 69-Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 70-Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 71-Sarenco, Ventabren performance (Box 3)
  - 72-Sarenco, Umbertine performance (Box 3)
  - 73-Sarenco, Hans Clavin (Box 3)
  - 74-Sarenco's father, Sarenco, sconosciuto (Box 3)
  - 75-Sarenco, Milano performance (Box 3)
  - 76-Sarenco e Gianfranco Composti (Box 3)
  - 77-Aldo Mondino, Gianni Sassi, Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 78-Sarenco e Cheff Mwai (Box 3)
  - 79-Enrico Mascelloni e Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 80-Aldo Mondino, Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 81-Adriano Parise, Aldo Mondino (Box 3)
  - 82-Cheff Mwai (Box 3)
  - 83-Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 84-Sarenco, Duchamp performance (Box 3)
  - 85-Sarenco, Duchamp performance (Box 3)
  - 86-Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 87-Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 88-Sarenco, Duchamp performance (Box 3)
  - 89-Jean-François Bory (Box 3)
  - 90-Jean-François Bory (Box 3)
  - 91-Piero Matarrese, Cheff Mwai (Box 3)
  - 92-Cheff Mwai (Box 3)
  - 93-Cheff Mwai (Box 3)
  - 94-Cheff Mwai (Box 3)
  - 95-Piero Matarrese, Cheff Mwai (Box 3)
  - 96-Cheff Mwai (Box 3)
  - 97-Cheff Mwai (Box 3)
  - 98-Giuseppe Desiato (Box 3)
  - 99-Sarenco, Giuseppe Desiato (Box 3)
  - 100-Aldo Mondino, Giuseppe Desiato, Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 101-Lamberto Pignotti, Aldo Mondino (Box 3)
  - 102-Lamberto Pignotti, Tomaso Binga, Giovanni Fontana (Box 3)
  - 103-Peter Frank, Sarenco, Jean-François Bory, Julien Blaine (Box 3)
  - 104-Enrico Mascelloni, Julien Blaine, Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 105-Sarenco, Enrico Mascelloni, Julien Blaine (Box 3)
  - 106-Julien Blaine, Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 107-Julien Blaine (Box 3)
  - 108-Sarenco, Julien Blaine, Eugenio Miccini, Grazia Azzali, Mauro Dal Fior, Joan Brossa (Box 3)
  - 109-Hans Clavin, Julien Blaine, Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 110-Franco Riccardo, Julien Blaine, Jean-François Bory (Box 3)
  - 111-Julien Blaine (Box 3)
  - 112-Julien Blaine (Box 3)
  - 113-Franco Riccardo, Julien Blaine, Jeann-François Bory (Box 3)
  - 114-Sarenco, Julien Blaine (Box 3)
  - 115-Julien Blaine, Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 116-Julien Blaine (Box 3)
  - 117-Julien Blaine (Box 3)
  - 118-Julien Blaine, Sarenco, Adriano Parise, Mario Dondero, Hans Clavin, X, Fabrizio Garghetti (Box 3)
  - 119-Julien Blaine (Box 3)
  - 120-Julien Blaine (Box 3)
  - 121-Julien Blaine (Box 3)
  - 122-Julien Blaine (Box 3)
  - 123-Julien Blaine (Box 3)
  - 124-Enrico Mascelloni, Julien Blaine, Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 125-Sarenco, Julien Blaine (Box 3)
  - 126-Shozo Shimamoto (Box 3)
  - 127-Sarenco, Pierre Garnier (Box 3)
  - 128-Julien Blaine, Sarenco, Bartolomé Ferrando (Box 3)
  - 129-Shozo Shimamoto (Box 3)
  - 130-Ugo Carrega, Sarenco, Beppe Morra, Ignazio Moncada (Box 3)
  - 131-Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 132-Shozo Shimamoto (Box 3)
  - 133-Shozo Shimamoto (Box 3)
  - 134-Shozo Shimamoto (Box 3)
  - 135-Adriana Casu, Bartolomé Ferrando (Box 3)
  - 136-Bartolomé Ferrando, Julien Blaine, Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 137-X, Bartolomé Ferrando, Sarenco, Julien Blaine (Box 3)
  - 138-Bartolomé Ferrando in performance (Box 3)
  - 139-Luc Fierens, Giovanni Fontana (Box 3)
  - 140-Giovanni Fontana, Hans Clavin, Jean-François Bory (Box 3)
  - 141-Maurizio Cattelan, Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 142-Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 143-Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 144-Sarenco with the Mau Mau freedom Fighters (Box 3)
  - 145-Sarenco e Enrico Mascelloni in performance (Box 3)
  - 146-Sarenco, Peshawar performance (Box 3)
  - 147-Sarenco ed Enrico Mascelloni, Latore performance (Box 3)
  - 148-Sarenco ed Enrico Mascelloni, Peshawar performance (Box 3)
  - 149-Sarenco, Allahu Akbar performance (Box 3)
  - 150-Sarenco, Colognola performance (Box 3)
  - 151-Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 152-Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 153-Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 154-Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 155-Jean-François Bory, Julien Blaine (Box 3)
  - 156-Shozo Shimamoto (Box 3)
  - 157-Shozo Shimamoto (Box 3)
  - 158-Shozo Shimamoto (Box 3)
  - 159-Almagul Menlibayeva (Box 3)
  - 160-Almagul Menlibayeva (Box 3)
  - 161-Almagul Menlibayeva (Box 3)
  - 162-Almagul Menlibayeva (Box 3)
  - 163-Almagul Menlibayeva (Box 3)
  - 164-Almagul Menlibayeva (Box 3)
  - 165-Almagul Melibayeva (Box 3)
  - 166-Almagul Menlibayeva (Box 3)
  - 167-Almagul Menlibayeva (Box 3)
  - 168-Almagul Menlibyeva (Box 3)
  - 169-Almagul Menlibayeva (Box 3)
  - 170-Almagul Menlibayeva (Box 3)
  - 171-Almagul Menlibayeva (Box 3)
  - 172-Gérard Fioretti (Box 3)
  - 173-Gérard Fioretti (Box 3)
  - 174-Gérard Fioretti (Box 3)
  - 175-Gérard Fioretti (Box 3)
  - 176-Gérard Fioretti (Box 3)
  - 177-Gérard Fioretti (Box 3)
  - 178-Gérard Fioretti (Box 3)
  - 179-Gérard Fioretti (Box 3)
  - 180-Almagul Menlibayeva (Box 3)
  - 181-Shozo Shimamoto e Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 182-Erbozyn Meldibekov (Box 3)
  - 183-Erbozyn Meldibekov (Box 3)
  - 184-Erbozyn Meldibekov (Box 3)
  - 185-Erbozyn Meldibekov (Box 3)
  - 186-Erbozyn Meldibekov (Box 3)
  - 187-Sarenco e Pierre Garnier (Box 3)
  - 188-Sarenco, Pierre Garnier, Ilse Garnier (Box 3)
  - 189-Giovanni Fontana e Jean-François Bory (Box 3)
  - 190-Franca Vignati, Ugo Carrega, Sarenco, Ignazio Moncada (Box 3)
  - 191-Sarenco e Pierre Garnier (Box 3)
  - 192-Julien Blaine, Sarenco, Bartolomé Ferrando (Box 3)
  - 193-Julien Blaine, Sarenco, Bartolomé Ferrando (Box 3)
  - 194-Julien Blaine, Sarenco, Bartolomé Ferrando (Box 3)
  - 195-Julien Blaine, Sarenco, Bartolomé Ferrando (Box 3)
  - 196-Bartlomé Ferrando, Julien Blaine, Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 197-Bartolomé Ferrando, Julien Blaine, Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 198-Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 199-Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 200-Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 201-Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 202-Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 203-Sarenco- (Box 3)
  - 204-Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 205-Sarenco e Seni Camara (Box 3)
  - 206-Sarenco e Emmett Williams (Box 3)
  - 207-Sarenco e Emmett Williams (Box 3)
  - 208-Auguste Galli, X,X,Sarenco,X (Box 3)
  - 209-Sarenco e Sergio Dangelo (Box 3)
  - 210-Sarenco's Muslim Marriage (Box 3)
  - 211-Sarenco's Muslim Marriage (Box 3)
  - 212-Sarenco's Muslim Marriage (Box 3)
  - 213-Sergio Dangelo e Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 214-Sarenco e Sergio Dangelo (Box 3)
  - 215-Sarenco's Muslim Marriage (Box 3)
  - 216-Sarenco's Muslim Marriage (Box 3)
  - 217-Sarenco fishing (Box 3)
  - 218-Aldo Tagliaferri, Sarenco, N.V. Parekh (Box 3)
  - 219-Sarenco fishing (Box 3)
  - 220-Sarenco fisherman (Box 3)
  - 221-Sarenco e David Ochieng (Box 3)
  - 222-Sarenco e N.V. Parekh (Box 3)
  - 223-Luigi Bonotto, Aldo Tagliaferro, N.V. Parekh,Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 224-Un'opera di Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 225-Installazione di E.A. Vigo (Box 3)
  - 226-Jiri Valoch: 'Forest piece' (Box 3)
  - 227-Jiri Valoch: 'Forest piece' (Box 3)
  - 228-Un'opera di Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 229-Paolo Berardelli, Sarenco, Giorgio Cortenova, Aldo Mondino, Ignazio Moncada (Box 3)
  - 230-Jiri Valoch:'Forest piece' (Box 3)
  - 231-Giuseppe Desiato, Sarenco, Aldo Mondino (Box 3)
  - 232-Opera di E.A. Vigo (Box 3)
  - 233-Opera di E.A. Vigo (Box 3)
  - 234-Opera di E.A. Vigo (Box 3)
  - 235-Opera di E.A. Vigo (Box 3)
  - 236-Opera di E.A. Vigo (Box 3)
  - 237-Opera di E.A. Vigo (Box 3)
  - 238-Opera di E.A. Vigo (Box 3)
  - 239-Opera di E.A. Vigo (Box 3)
  - 240-Harald Szeemann davanti a una installazione di Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 241-Innocente, Harald Szeemann (Box 3)
  - 242-Auguste Galli, Sarenco, Ladislav Novak, X,X,X,X (Box 3)
  - 243-Sarenco, Ladislav Novak, X,X (Box 3)
  - 244-Sarenco, Ladislav Novak (Box 3)
  - 245-Harald Szeemann a Venezia (Box 3)
  - 246-Sarenco, Innocente, Harald Szeemann (Box 3)
  - 247-Un'opera di Wolf Vostell (Box 3)
  - 248-Omar A. Ronda, Sarenco, Enrico Mascelloni, X (Box 3)
  - 249-Julien Blaine, Sarenco, X (Box 3)
  - 250-Julien Blaine, Sarenco, X (Box 3)
  - 251-Julien Blaine, Sarenco, X (Box 3)
  - 252-Richard Martel, Giovanni Fontana (Box 3)
  - 253-Giovanni Fontana, John Giorno (Box 3)
  - 254-Julien Blaine, Giovanni Fontana (Box 3)
  - 255-Giovanni Fontana, Sarenco, Jean-François Bory, Julien Blaine (Box 3)
  - 256-Edgardo Antonio Vigo (Box 3)
  - 257-Julien Blaine, X, Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 258-Dossou Amidou, X, Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 259-X, Ugo Carrega, X (Box 3)
  - 260-X, Ugo Carrega, X (Box 3)
  - 261-Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 262-X, Esther Mahlangu, Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 263-Sarenco, Twins Seven Seven (Box 3)
  - 264-Sarenco, Esther Mahlangu, X (Box 3)
  - 265-Sarenco, Seni Camara, X (Box 3)
  - 266-Tita Mbaye, Sarenco, Mandemory (Box 3)
  - 267-Julien Blaine (Box 3)
  - 268-Vittore Baroni, Luc Fierens, X (Box 3)
  - 269-Installazione di Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 270-Installazione di Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 271-Installazione di Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 272-Installazione di Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 273-Installazione di Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 274-Installazione di Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 275-Installazione di Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 276-Installazione di Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 277-Installazione di Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 278-Installazione di Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 279-Installazione di Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 280-Installazione di Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 281-Installazione di Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 282-Installazione di Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 283-Installazione di Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 284-Installazione di Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 285-Installazione di Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 286-Installazione di Sarenco (Box 3)
  - 287-Installazione di Sarenco (Box 3)